# Anastasia Sirman

New York, New York | 347-825-9968 | anyasirman@outlook.com Linkedin | Github | Blog| anastasiasirman.com

## **FullStack Software Engineer**

Full stack software engineer with experience in React, Express, Node, Rails, and SQL. I love building applications from the ground up with a focus on clean code and user experience. I have experience building fast frontends with intuitive UI, server-side applications, and REST APIs.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Ruby, Rails, SQL, Javascript, React, CSS, HTML, ExpressJS, NodeJS, Sequelize, Git, AWS S3

### **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

## Callbck- Github | Demo

Manages dance listings and application flow. (Rails, React, JWT, Active Storage, CSS, AWS S3)

- Integrated Amazon Web Services S3 to store uploaded images
- Action Cable to allow users to upload photos and PDFs to cloud storage
- Built authentication features with cookies and JWT for user sessions

•

## KonDi- Github | Demo

Store encrypted diary entries. (Rails, React, JWT, CSS, Active Record Encryption)

- Created client and user authentication protocols with JWT and cookies
- Protected user diary entries, and sensitive information with Active Record Encryption
- Added GPT3-generated graphics with React

## Banana- Github | Demo

E-commerce store (Express, PostgreSQL, React, JWT, CSS)

- Integrated Stripe API for a streamlined checkout experience
- Procedurally generated Stripe's integrated products
- Added user cart persistence with local storage
- Bulit custom routes with Express

### **EXPERIENCE**

 Walgreens
 Bronx, New York

 Shift Lead
 06/2021 - 07/2022

- Orchestrated store operations day to day with a decrease in employee turnover
- Communicated with corporate for weekly store adjustments and redistribution of assets

# **New Jersey Ballet**

Jersey City, New Jersey 12/2019 - 03/2020

CORPS de Ballet member

- Worked as part of a team to cohesively perform to sold-out shows
- Performed partnering routines with other corps members

### **EDUCATION**

**Flatiron School**Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails and JavaScript program

New York, New York

06/ 2022 - 10/2022

Havard CS50 Online

Computer science 101 courses work through data structures, algorithms, memory allocation, and procedural programming.

### **Joffrey Ballet School**

New York, New York 09/2018 - 12/2019

Ballet, jazz, contemporary, pas de Deux, intensive live program working to build professional dancers.